http://www.bigmoviezone.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Big Movie Zone's policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users.
This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how
we use it.
There are cases where BMZ may ask for personal information such as your name, location, email address, and age. For example, we request personal information on our feedback forms and for entrance in our contests. We needs to collect this information for fulfilling prizes, tracking and verifying compliance with BMZ policies, and for federal, state and local laws. We use contact data from our contests only to notify the user of contest results or to include the user on our newsletter mailing list. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings through the unsubscribe link found within our mailings. Under some circumstances users under the age of 18 will not be allowed to participate in contests. Users under the age of 16 MUST ask their parents' permission before participating in any contest.
We will not disclose your personal information to third parties with the following exceptions: we may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) BMZ's rights or property, other BMZ users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. BMZ may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
BMZ may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. This data is used to customize BMZ's content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users.
Home  |  Contact Us  |  Who We Are  |  Advertise  |  Copyright  |  Site Map  |  Privacy Policy
© 2006-2016 Big Movie Zone, All Rights Reserved.
